[{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "66d631a76d39de22d7d95a62"
  },
  "language": "English",
  "question": "Nouns that indicate the names of people, countries and places are called:",
  "answers": [
    "Proper nouns",
    "Common nouns",
    "Abstract nouns"
  ],
  "mul": "y",
  "correct": "Proper nouns"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "66d631a76d39de22d7d95a63"
  },
  "language": "English",
  "question": "Plural of the nouns bus and sheep are:",
  "answers": [
    "buss, sheep",
    "buses, sheep",
    "buses, sheeps"
  ],
  "mul": "y",
  "correct": "buses, sheep"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "66d631a76d39de22d7d95a64"
  },
  "language": "English",
  "question": "We use definite article THE when talking about a person \n we do not know or whom we are mentioning for the first time.\n Example: There is THE boy in the street.",
  "answers": [],
  "mul": "tf",
  "correct": "False"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "66d631a76d39de22d7d95a65"
  },
  "language": "English",
  "question": "Which sentence is correct?",
  "answers": [
    "Tom plays a football very well.",
    "Tom plays the football very well.",
    "Tom plays football very well."
  ],
  "mul": "y",
  "correct": "Tom plays football very well."
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "66d631a76d39de22d7d95a66"
  },
  "language": "English",
  "question": "Only the first three ordinal numbers in the English language do not end with the suffix -th.",
  "answers": [],
  "mul": "tf",
  "correct": "True"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "66d631a76d39de22d7d95a67"
  },
  "language": "English",
  "question": "We use ordinal numbers for centuries.\n Example: The 21st century.",
  "answers": [],
  "mul": "tf",
  "correct": "True"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "66d631a76d39de22d7d95a68"
  },
  "language": "English",
  "question": "Fill in the gap with necessary article:\n I am ___ student.",
  "answers": [],
  "mul": "n",
  "correct": "a"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "66d631a76d39de22d7d95a69"
  },
  "language": "English",
  "question": "Fill in the gap in the conditional sentence (verb boil):\n The water ___ if you heat it to 100 degrees.",
  "answers": [],
  "mul": "n",
  "correct": "boils"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "66d631a76d39de22d7d95a6a"
  },
  "language": "English",
  "question": "Solve the comparation:\n Bad - worse - the ___",
  "answers": [],
  "mul": "n",
  "correct": "worst"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "66d631a76d39de22d7d95a6b"
  },
  "language": "English",
  "question": "Write the personal pronounce WE to fill in the blank:\n Maria wants ___ to bre there at 5.",
  "answers": [],
  "mul": "n",
  "correct": "us"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "66d631a76d39de22d7d95a6c"
  },
  "language": "English",
  "question": "Choose the correct conditional.",
  "answers": [
    "If I had a car, I would visit you tomorrow!",
    "If I have a car, I visit you tomorrow!",
    "If I had had a car, I would've visited you tomorrow!"
  ],
  "mul": "y",
  "correct": "If I had a car, I would visit you tomorrow!"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "66d631a76d39de22d7d95a6d"
  },
  "language": "Serbian",
  "question": "Select a noun that has feminine gender",
  "answers": [
    "more",
    "kolač",
    "haljina"
  ],
  "mul": "y",
  "correct": "haljina"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "66d631a76d39de22d7d95a6e"
  },
  "language": "Serbian",
  "question": "Number one(1) - in nominative, masculine gender is:",
  "answers": [
    "jedna",
    "jedan",
    "jedni"
  ],
  "mul": "y",
  "correct": "jedan"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "66d631a76d39de22d7d95a6f"
  },
  "language": "Serbian",
  "question": "Possessive pronouns are obtained by aksing:",
  "answers": [
    "ČIJI?, ČIJA?, ČIJE?",
    "KO, šTA",
    "KOJI, ČIJI"
  ],
  "mul": "y",
  "correct": "ČIJI?, ČIJA?, ČIJE?"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "66d631a76d39de22d7d95a70"
  },
  "language": "Serbian",
  "question": "Select one impersonal verb form:",
  "answers": [
    "Prezent",
    "Aorist",
    "Infinitiv"
  ],
  "mul": "y",
  "correct": "Infinitiv"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "66d631a76d39de22d7d95a71"
  },
  "language": "Serbian",
  "question": "There are seven cases in Serbian language",
  "answers": [],
  "mul": "tf",
  "correct": "True"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "66d631a76d39de22d7d95a72"
  },
  "language": "Serbian",
  "question": "We write 1.,2.,3. instead of 1,2,3.",
  "answers": [],
  "mul": "tf",
  "correct": "False"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "66d631a76d39de22d7d95a73"
  },
  "language": "Serbian",
  "question": "Possessive adjectives derived from proper nouns\n are written with a capital letter.",
  "answers": [],
  "mul": "tf",
  "correct": "True"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "66d631a76d39de22d7d95a74"
  },
  "language": "Serbian",
  "question": "All basic numbers can be changed by cases.",
  "answers": [],
  "mul": "tf",
  "correct": "False"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "66d631a76d39de22d7d95a75"
  },
  "language": "Serbian",
  "question": "Fill in the gap:\nThe first Grammar case in Serbian is ___.",
  "answers": [],
  "mul": "n",
  "correct": "nominativ"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "66d631a76d39de22d7d95a76"
  },
  "language": "Serbian",
  "question": "Make comparative from adjective skup - ___.",
  "answers": [],
  "mul": "n",
  "correct": "skuplji"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "66d631a76d39de22d7d95a77"
  },
  "language": "Serbian",
  "question": "Plural of the word krompir is ___.",
  "answers": [],
  "mul": "n",
  "correct": "krompiri"
}]